Guide to the Jean-Pierre Habicht papers, 1940-2007
Habicht, Jean-Pierre papers
- Series IX. Center for Research and development in Nutrition (CRDN) Reports
  - Indonesia, October 1982 (Box 10, Folder 35)